antezeta.com 2012-06-21

# » Antezeta - Data Privacy Statement

#### [Sign up](http://antezeta.com/news-signup.html "Antezeta Newsletter Sign-up") now for our free newsletter!

  * Keep up to date on news from Antezeta!

This page explains our privacy policy and how we will use any information resulting from your visit to our website.

  1. [Sites covered by this Privacy Statement](http://antezeta.com/privacy.html#p1 "Jump directly to the topic")
  2. [What information do we collect?](http://antezeta.com/privacy.html#p2 "Jump directly to the topic")
  3. [How we use your information](http://antezeta.com/privacy.html#p3 "Jump directly to the topic")
  4. [Who we share your information with](http://antezeta.com/privacy.html#p4 "Jump directly to the topic")
  5. [Inquires](http://antezeta.com/privacy.html#p5 "Jump directly to the topic")
  6. [Changes to this Privacy Statement](http://antezeta.com/privacy.html#p6 "Jump directly to the topic")

## Sites covered by this Privacy Statement

This Privacy Statement applies to all Antezeta owned websites and domains.

### Links to non-Antezeta websites

It does not cover external websites mentioned in links throughout this website which are not controlled by Antezeta.

## What information do we collect?

### Non-personal information

If you are a user who has not logged into our site, we only capture usage and service operation data that is not associated with a specific personal identity. We collect and analyze non-personal information to evaluate how visitors use Antezeta websites. This data includes your IP address, URL "page" request information, browser type, operating system and referring link, if any. We aggregate this data to compile site usage statistics as part of a site improvement program.

### Reserved Client Area users

If you login to our reserved client area, we also capture your technical username. Since we must provide you with the username, your use of a username results from an existing relationship with us.

### Contact

Our site offers the possibility for you to contact us via e-mail. Should you so contact us, rest assured that we will not pass your information on to third parties without your prior consent, as in accordance with European data protection acts.

### Cookies

This site may use cookies to offer personalization for returning site visitors and to improve the quality of site statistics. For more information about cookies, see any of the following cookies resources.

  * U.S. Department of Energy Computer Incident Advisory Capability Information Bulletin I-034 Internet Cookies
  * The original Netscape Cookie Specification

#### Google Advertising & Cookies

Some pages on this domain may carry Google advertising to offset the costs of maintaing the content. Please refer to Google's [help documentation](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/) on the subject for current information on their use of cookies in their advertising system.

## How we use your information

Non-personal data is aggregated for reporting about our website usability and effectiveness. It is used as part of a program to continually improve the quality of the site and its content in order to better server the site's users.

Personal information given is used to service your requests.

## Who we share your information with

Antezeta will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. Antezeta will not share your personal information with third parties except if necessary in responding to your requests for information or services. Your permission will be requested before information is shared.

## Inquires

If you have a question or complaint about this _Privacy Statement_ or about the site, you can [contact us](http://antezeta.com/contacts.html "Contact Antezeta").

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

This policy may change from time to time. If it changes in any way, we will place the updated version here. Regularly reviewing this page when you visit our site ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.

Last updated: 2005-06-25.

* * *

* * *

* * *
